bemovies.tv 2011-05-14

# Download best movies from BeMovies

## Introductions

This privacy policy sets out how bemovies.tv uses and protects any information that you give when you use this website. bemovies.tv is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. bemovies.tv collects your information automatically for understanding your needs and provides you with a better service.

## IP addresses

When you access bemovies.tv from a computer, mobile phone, or other device, we may collect information from that device about your browser type, location, and IP address, as well as the pages you visit. bemovies.tv receives IP addresses from all users because this information is automatically reported by your browser each time you view a web page.

## Cookies

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyze web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences. We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyze data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.

## Personal information

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. bemovies.tv collects your personal information in the following ways:  
\- whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes  
\- if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen. If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.

## Financial information

bemovies.tv uses SSL (Secure Socket Layer) encryption when transmitting such information as financial services information or payment information. bemovies.tv does not permanently store credit card information on its servers. All credit card numbers and identifying financial data are passed directly to the site where credit card orders are processed for all bemovies.tv customers.

## Other information

bemovies.tv may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

The materials on the bemovies.tv may not be republished, copied, printed or used in any way, on any medium and under any circumstances without written consent. Fore more information please visit bemovies.tv's Terms of use. bemovies.tv may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from 01.09.2010.
